[{"answer": "No.", "docId": "121108pmt", "aSentId": 67, "question": "Have you ever seen one quite that candid and raw?", "qSentId": 66}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, I think that we all think of and we talk about the president's coolness, and with due respect to Dan, whom I enormously admire, let's not confuse composure with coolness.", "docId": "121108pmt", "aSentId": 80, "question": "What do you want Barack Obama now to really achieve that will be his legacy?", "qSentId": 79}, {"answer": "Well, there is that, but we need to keep in mind that second terms for presidents generally speaking historically have not turned out that well.", "docId": "121108pmt", "aSentId": 94, "question": "Well, they failed and there is a certain liberation that comes with being re-elected, isn't there, an empowerment that says OK, well, stuff you, I'm back for four years and I'm going to make things happen now?", "qSentId": 93}, {"answer": "I'm doing well, Piers.", "docId": "121108pmt", "aSentId": 142, "question": "Tim Pawlenty, how are you?", "qSentId": 141}, {"answer": "Well, of course, election results are a little like post-modern art.", "docId": "121108pmt", "aSentId": 154, "question": "Why was that belief so built on sand, do you think?", "qSentId": 153}, {"answer": "Well, let's give some examples, Piers, of where the two sides could come together.", "docId": "121108pmt", "aSentId": 182, "question": "How long can the Republicans, led by the Grover Norquist gang, sustain a position of there is zero movement or flexibility for any increased taxation when most Americans think it's perfectly reasonable given there's a $16 trillion debt that the wealthiest should pay more tax?", "qSentId": 181}, {"answer": "I think it's fair to say, Piers, that the Republicans aren't going to raise tax rates but they are willing to look at raising some revenues along the lines that I've described and if you get to the same result, I think that's a good step forward in the interest of trying to find a bipartisan solution.", "docId": "121108pmt", "aSentId": 194, "question": "What is the difference?", "qSentId": 193}, {"answer": "I didn't say I wasn't impressed by them.", "docId": "121108pmt", "aSentId": 229, "question": "What's the matter with you, man?", "qSentId": 228}, {"answer": "I definitely think Mitt Romney could do that.", "docId": "121108pmt", "aSentId": 240, "question": "Did you think Mitt Romney could ever do that?", "qSentId": 239}, {"answer": "You know, I think this is an election about the economy.", "docId": "121108pmt", "aSentId": 307, "question": "Do you understand why so many women did?", "qSentId": 306}, {"answer": "Well, I think that we may be missing something.", "docId": "121108pmt", "aSentId": 339, "question": "Then he had to slowly back pedal again, by which time really, in terms of principle, he's toast, isn't he?", "qSentId": 338}, {"answer": "Sure.", "docId": "121108pmt", "aSentId": 380, "question": "So Brian, why is this a good thing then, to legalize cannabis?", "qSentId": 379}, {"answer": "Well, I think legalization is really an extreme answer.", "docId": "121108pmt", "aSentId": 391, "question": "Kevin Sabet, why is it a terrible idea?", "qSentId": 390}, {"answer": "I think they're very different.", "docId": "121108pmt", "aSentId": 407, "question": "If you overdo alcohol, if you're a young person, for example?", "qSentId": 406}, {"answer": "Some similar --", "docId": "121108pmt", "aSentId": 413, "question": "They would suffer similar issues, wouldn't they?", "qSentId": 412}, {"answer": "That's absolutely true.", "docId": "121108pmt", "aSentId": 421, "question": "Isn't that the argument?", "qSentId": 420}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, I'm not saying to jail marijuana users.", "docId": "121108pmt", "aSentId": 433, "question": "Isn't it a waste of law enforcement finances and resources?", "qSentId": 432}, {"answer": "It was certainly a little stressful.", "docId": "121108pmt", "aSentId": 478, "question": "What were the feelings?", "qSentId": 477}, {"answer": "I mean it's time to move on.", "docId": "121108pmt", "aSentId": 488, "question": "What did you mean by that?", "qSentId": 487}, {"answer": "Well, he certainly has a lot on his plate, you know, with the economy and the situation we have, the approaching fiscal cliff.", "docId": "121108pmt", "aSentId": 514, "question": "Do you think now is the time, now that he has got another four-year term, to really do something really meaningful?", "qSentId": 513}]